Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show. Let's let's address it out
of the gate.
Let's talk about the biggest free speech
issue right now in the world.
Let's
tackle it headon.
Everyone is talking about it. Everyone
wants to know what it means.
I was fired from the Riad Comedy
Festival.
It is the most important free speech
news.
Everybody has a take. Everyone has an
opinion. It's inescapable. Go to a
lunch. It comes up. You're at a
christening. You think you're safe.
You're not. Did you hear comedian
podcaster
Tim Dylan fired from Saudi Arabia's
first comedy festival? Shocking
developments. What does it mean? What
does it mean?
I'll tell you how it went down
and then we'll address that thing at ABC
with Kimmel. I also heard there's an
issue there. But
my agent called me and uh told me
first of all, I'm going to I'll lay out
the whole thing.
I was supposed to perform in Dubai. I
mixed up Dubai and I said Abu Dhabi.
Apparently, this is a big deal over
there. This is like a real problem. My
agent called me and he goes, "You you
sit on Joe Rogan that you were
performing in Abu Dhabi and it's you're
actually performing in Dubai. They're
cities and they have a rivalry." And I
go, "Dude, who gives a [__] What do I
stop? I made a mistake.
This is not a malicious
slander. It's a mistake." He goes,
"Well, they're very angry and they sent
an email that you need to be
controlled." I said, "Well, good luck.
Whatever. I don't have to do it. I don't
care.
And then he called me a few days later
and I thought he was going to talk about
the Kimmel thing. I thought he was going
to talk about the Kimmel thing.
Um but he called me and he said there
they heard what you said about their
them having slaves.
And I said I was being positive about
it. I was defending them.
He goes, "Well, I know that. I know you
were defending." I said I was defending
them for having slaves. I literally said
slaves are probably hard workers and for
the most part agreeable,
but they didn't like that.
You can literally support somebody too
much. I've learned this. You can
actually, by the way, in life this
happens. Too many compliments, too much,
too much support, and then they turn on
you.
I was saying that slaves were proud of
some of the buildings they built.
That's what I was saying. I was saying
that if I was a slave, not that I want
to be, if I was a slave, and I built a
really nice thing, I might say to my
slave children, "Daddy built that."
That's what I was saying. That I would
have said, "Hey, daddy built that."
When my slave children said, "Oh, look
at that." I'd say, "You know, daddy
built that."
I was going that angle. Apparently, this
got to the people in Saudi Arabia and
they were unhappy about it.
They're huge fans of comedy over there.
Now, I am very clear about the way I
will do a gig. If I accept a gig, I am
not going to break the rules of the gig.
meaning Amish people call me, they go,
"Tim, we're gonna pay you a lot of
money. We want you to perform
uh in the Amish
Pennsylvania Dutch country, but we're
Amish, so we don't want to hear about
iPhones
or or Khi, which they should hear about.
It's phenomenal this Cali. We'll get to
it later. But if that was a rule, I
would respect it while I'm there."
While I'm in Pennsylvania Dutch country,
eating shoefly pie, respecting their
culture,
you have a culture. You've got Sharia
law. Would I like Sharia law? No, I
don't want it. Actually, I don't want
it. I'm good. But you have it. So, I
don't It's not like I have bits in my
act about the prophet anyway.
So, I'm I I certainly wasn't going to
show up in your country and insult
uh the people that are paying me the
money. One, it's illegal.
So, I wasn't really planning to go to a
Saudi jail.
But on my own show, in my own country
where I have the freedom to speak and
say the things I want, I'm going to be
funny and I'm going to be who I am. And
if it you're not buying that, you don't
have the right to tell me on my own
show. People were coming up to me
saying, "Why would you go to that
country? They have slaves in Tribeca."
They're assaulting me, these people. I'm
just leaving uh a lunch and they're
coming out. They have slaves, they say.
And of course, I I addressed it
in a funny way and they fired me. And
then they told me they go the my agents
they all call me you don't have to talk
about this they say don't talk about it
remember when you talked about Joker I
said what they go it hurts you to talk
about these things in what what is in
what is even left you bums this the only
thing left is what I'm doing nobody what
what are you talking about
so and what I mean by that is Like
there's the the the business doesn't
have any teeth anymore. They can't tell
me what to do or say. What? They're not
even offering anything. They're not even
offering anything. We don't want people
thinking you're a problem. But they
already How do they not think that? How
could they not think that? How a goo a a
Google of me and a a read a a 60sec
scroll.
You buy me, you buy what I'm gonna do.
Joker was a bad movie.
Why would I lie and say it's good?
Everyone thought it was bad in the
world.
Okay, every article that came out was
like, "Hey, this thing sucks. What was I
supposed to do?" By the way, I was in it
for a second and I made no money.
What loyalty am I supposed to have? and
the director was mean to me.
So, I'm supposed to go out there and
talk about how great it is. Well, you're
actually just misunderstanding the
movie. It's actually really good. The
Joker doing dance numbers is good. It's
good that it doesn't have a plot. It's
actually good.
It doesn't work.
Who the [__] wants to watch that, you
know? So they, you know, they were like,
"Well, you don't have to tell people
that you're not going because, you know,
we don't want people thinking you're
that person that gets fired." Yeah,
whatever. Think it. What do I give a
[__]
I mean, what? Who cares? I'm going to
get fired again. I'm going to get fired
again from people that are not even
Saudis. I'm going to get fired by people
who don't chop hands off. I'm going to
get fired by reasonable people.
I'm going to get fired by people that
that don't practice Sharia law. I will
be fired by many races and religions.
I'm going to be fired by others.
I will This is the most controversial
the people who fire me will ever be. Let
me relish in this. Let Let's take this
win.
The future people that fire me will be
good mothers and fathers, family people
who probably fire me for a completely
rational reason. You know, I you know, I
just rolled out of bed and I just
decided to do something they didn't like
and that's completely fine. It is what
it is.
This is the first time I've been fired
uh by people that actually do really bad
things.
So, let's take this win.
Let's take this win. I'm now with Iran.
Iran's against them. I'm with Iran now.
You've pushed me into the bosom of Iran.
Do you understand that?
you. I'm going to Thran to do their
comedy festival. I don't care.
I'm being pushed into the arms of Iran.
Those types of Muslims. What are those
ones called? Shia. I'm Shia now. I was
going to be Sunni. I think Saudi is
Sunni and Iran is Shia. Right. Yes.
Maybe
I'm Shia now.
Shiite.
Right. Shia, that's what I am now.
Because you've done this to me. You've
fired me and created a Shia problem. I'm
a Shiite problem now. Batch.
So,
who cares? By the way, I get to keep My
agent knows this. He knows often if you
represent me, you're going to get calls
that people are unhappy. He just thought
it would be like the usual suspects, the
people around this town, this
dispiriting dump called Los Angeles. He
thought it was going to be those people
at the, you know, whatever the Riviera
Country Club calling me and going, "We
don't really, this guy's like, what is
he doing? Why did he have Kansas so and
why does he open his mouth? What's wrong
with him? Why is he dressed up like a
Muslim then a Jew? What's going on? I
don't get it." That's the normal calls.
He didn't think he was going to get a
call from the Middle East.
He didn't think I was going to get fired
by a theocracy in the Middle East.
Neither did I. But I'm with Iran now.
That's what happens. This is
geopolitics.
Do you understand? This is why the
Middle East is so effed up because
there's no [__] unity. There's no
goddamn unity.
That's all. So, I will be with Iran. I
don't know what to tell everyone.
Now, let's talk about Jimmy Kimmel,
which by the way, I think is much less
interesting than what happened to me,
but as usual, it's dominated the
headlines.
Jimmy Kimmel, I don't know Jimmy. I've
never met Jimmy.
I don't watch his show. Uh, my friends
know him and really, really like him as
a guy. He's like less annoying in real
life than he is on television. This is
what I hear from people who whom I
trust.
I think Jimmy was a funny guy. I don't
watch what he does now. It's very
political. It's very like kind of
annoying to most people. Even the people
that are in the middle, it's annoying to
people that are apolitical. It's
annoying. It's way over the top. Cole
Bayer, him, everybody went way over the
top. Doesn't matter. Doesn't matter. He
should still be on the air. And I'll get
to why.
But setting the stage here, they all
went way over the top. Johnny Carson
said years ago, I'm not political. I'm
here to put Americans to bed. These guys
went fully the other way. They alienated
half the country. It's their right, by
the way. It's their right. Is it a great
business move? Probably not. Probably
not. You know, if you opened the
pizzeria, you wouldn't call it like, you
know, [__] Trump pizza unless it was
like in Portland or something. You know,
if you're trying to appeal to a
demographic of people that is of many
political stripes, but they're not.
They've given up on that. That's fine.
That's their right. It's their right to
politicize their show to a point where
it's unwatchable. And by the way, that's
anyone's right. Okay, I'm going to play
the joke he made. It's a weird joke and
it's a not factually correct thing, but
here's why I'm going to not only defend
it, but I I think it is ridiculous to
pull this guy off the air. I think it's
ridiculous to pretend it was about
money. I think it's ridiculous to
pretend um that it's not a political hit
job. It's a political hit job and we
know it. Was was ABC is it the cash cow
it was 10 20 years ago? Absolutely not.
We know late night TV is dying. We know
all of that. That's not why this show
got yanked. And pretending it is is an
insult to people's intelligence. Okay?
It's an insult to people's intelligence.
This was a hit politically motivated it
job. Okay. It's
something that most people who talk for
a living should care about. If you talk
for a living, if you're making money,
entertaining people,
informing people, whatever it is you
think you're doing out there, anybody
who's doing that should care a little
bit about this. Let's watch um his joke
and then let's talk about the fallout.
We hit some new lows over the weekend
with the MAGA gang desperately trying to
characterize this kid who murdered
Charlie Kirk as anything other than one
of them and doing everything they can to
score political points from it. In
between the fingerpointing there was uh
grieving on Friday. The White House flew
the flags at half staff which got some
criticism but on a human level you can
see how hard the president is taking
this.
>> My condolences on the loss of your
friend Charlie Kirk. May I ask sir
personally, how are you holding up over
the last day and a half, sir?
>> I think very good. And by the way, right
there you see all the trucks. They've
just started construction of the new
ballroom for the White House, which is
something they've been trying to get, as
you know, for about 150 years. And it's
going to be a beauty.
>> Yes. He's at the fourth stage of grief.
Construction.
Demolition.
So, so here's the thing. Not a bad, you
know, it's it's a fun joke. The the the
setup to the joke where it's like
they're doing everything they can to
pretend this guy's not a MAGA guy.
Nobody thought this guy was a MAGA guy.
People thought he was a far-right
internet kid or a far-left internet kid.
No one thought he was like a card
carrying member of the MAGA group. So,
he's presenting the premise is is false.
Whatever. highlighting Trump's absurd
reaction when asked about Charlie Kirk,
you start talking about a ballroom,
dude. I mean, it's the president's own
words and then he does, you know, joke
about he's at, you know, he's at the
fifth stage of grief, fourth stage of
grief, construction, whatever
it, you know, it's it's kind of
now listen, it's it's being it's being
done in a climate that's very charged
emotionally. A guy got shot in the face.
His wife and kid will watch that for the
rest of their life. His wife and
children. The reactions to it, some of
them were abhorrent.
Some of the reactions to that were
including some of the mainstream media
obits were wild. Scoring political
points
on the guy with with a hole in his neck.
It's insane. And it's radicalized a lot
of people. And I'm not saying that was
everybody's reaction, but there were
people that reacted in a way. Now, by
the way, again, I I'll say it again. I
dressed up like a dead healthcare CEO
and saterized
how people feel when someone divisive
dies. I'm not against people doing
comedy, dark comedy, black comedy,
whatever you want to call it. I think
that the reactions to the Kirk thing
were people that were rationalizing,
not in a satirical way, but in a very
genuine way, rationalizing this guy
getting shot,
rationalizing him being killed, going,
"This is good. More of this. We need
this."
Okay.
And it
if you're if you're on that side where
you believe people that you don't like
should just get shot in the face.
Hey, what am I going to do? But it's
abhorrent to many people. It's not a
bit. It's not a joke. There is a
difference between a guy that's denying
lifesaving treatment to people who's a
healthc care CEO and a guy sitting on
college campuses debating kids. I don't
care what you think about his views.
There is a substantive difference
between those two people. And I wasn't
for the health care guy getting shot in
the head. I'm not for random people
getting shot in the head. I'd gladly pay
higher taxes if people got healthcare.
They never seem to. Taxes go up, but
they never seem to get that. But there
is a substantive difference. And the
idea that like people watched this whole
thing and some of the reactions were so
beyond the pale. It's going to be hard
to get those people to care about what's
happening to Kimmel. It is folks. I'll
tell you right now, you got to get
healthier about Lucy. 100% pure nicotine
always tobaccof free. Lucy breakers are
nicotine pouches with an extra surprise.
Each pouch each pouch holds a capsule
that can be broken up to release extra
flavor and hydration. and set yourself
up with a subscription and have Lucy
delivered straight to your door. God, I
love all of the Lucy flavors. It's
amazing. They're so good. I use a medium
strength. It's fine. Let's level up your
nicotine routine with Lucy. Go to
lucy.co/tim
promo code Tim Tim to get 20% off your
first order. Lucy has a 30-day refund
policy if you change your mind. Again,
that's lucy.co and use code tim to get
20% off.
And here comes the fine print. Lucy
products are only for adults of legal
age and every order is age verified.
warning. This product contains nicotine.
Nicotine is an addictive chemical.
People just want scalps.
That's what they want. No one in this
country has any interest in a bipartisan
standard where where where people
agree that they're going to be bothered.
America is about being bothered all the
time by people you don't like. People in
this country are going to make a lot of
money saying things you don't like. You
may be listening to one of them right
now. That is annoying.
People don't like that. They're never
going to like it. It'll never be it'll
never be
uh satisfying to hear someone you don't
agree with
say things you don't like and get paid
lots of money to do it. But that's part
of the deal. It's part of the reality of
living in America. Nobody likes this.
You either turn it off or you hate watch
it or you project onto this person
things that you believe they are. Maybe
you're right. Who knows? But you can't
you can't
think it's a great idea that the FCC,
the chairman of the FCC goes on a
podcast and goes, "We could do it the
easy way or the hard way. We could think
about revoking broadcast licenses." and
then pressures affiliates
to drop the show
because this guy said something the
president of the United States doesn't
like. The president of the United States
then also follows it up by going, "Hey,
uh, Seth Meyers, uh, you know, Fallon,
Seth Meyers, you're next."
You know, you're next. Do we have the
FCC? See if we can find the video of of
of uh Carr, I forget his first name.
Yeah. Going and talking about this.
Okay, let's listen to this.
There's actions that we can take on
licensed broadcasters. And frankly, I
think that it's it's it's really sort of
past time that a lot of these licensed
broadcasters themselves push back on
Comcast and Disney and say, "Listen, we
are going to preempt we are not going to
run Kimmel anymore until you straighten
this out because we we licensed
broadcaster are running the possibility
of fines or license revocation from the
FCC if we continue to run content that
ends up being a pattern of news
distortion." So, I think again Disney
needs to see some change here, but the
individual licensed stations that are
taking their content, it's time for them
to step up and say this, you know,
garbage uh to the extent that that's
what comes down the pipe in the future
isn't something that we think serves the
needs of our local communities. But, but
this sort of status quo is obviously not
not acceptable.
>> They're building uh they're building
China.
It's what they're building. It's why all
of the tech people decided they were
Republicans.
It's why
um all of the the contracts are going to
build AI models
uh that look at speech that they don't
like from students that attend to
protest. They're building China
and they don't want you to notice. And
if they can weaponize politics
so that you stop caring,
they can transform America into
something that's kind of unrecognizable.
This isn't without precedent. During the
2020s,
lunatics ran through a lot of the
institutions in America, from the media
to the universities, demanding that
people they disagreed with be fired.
They demanded those people be
deplatformed. They demanded those people
be made, you know, into
um
sacrifices publicly. Those people, they
wanted those people to be broke. They
wanted those people's families uh to be
targeted and harassed. And we watched
this in the 2020s. And it was disturbing
to me. I remember the Coington kids.
That grimacing little kid was standing
there and the Native Americans beating
the drum in his face. And then
celebrities, people I know were calling
for the doxing of that literal child and
his family who then upon further
reflection didn't do anything wrong.
This is a a human
impulse. It's a human impulse to get
whipped up into a frenzy and join a mob
and run around with pitchforks and
proclaim that you are morally superior
to other people. This is something human
beings enjoy doing. There's not that
many things that get people off,
you know. This is one of them. going and
and and and joining picking up a
pitchfork and running down the street
with the mob is something that people
get great enjoyment out of. It's fun.
They like it. They like tearing people
limb from limb.
And the problem with that is that it
doesn't end. See, it doesn't end. The
left does it to the right. The right
does it to the left. And then eventually
the government decides that people hate
each other in this country enough that
the government can then chop this thing
up,
sell it for parts
while you all hate each other and fight
each other. They can hand the country
over to oligarchs. Many of them are
friends. They all have dinner in
Washington DC.
They're all talking about how they reach
out to people in the media, people like
me, you know, they reach out to
everybody, and they tell you that it's
going to be good, that they are the
guardians of free speech. They care
about your ability to say things that
ruffle feathers. They're with you
and
they're actors.
And behind them are very wealthy people.
Some of whom you know, many of whom you
don't, by the way, and I don't. And we
could look them up and have trouble
finding them. Not in some crazy
conspiracy Knights Templar way, but in
the genuine way of like many of the
people who have huge ownership stakes in
companies are not public figures. They
exist on the periphery. They have large
sums of money and they're pretty quiet
about it. But they funnel that money
into places and they strangle
industries and all these people want to
merge. They want to do mergers with
their companies. They want to monopolize
industries. They want government money
and they want government grants. So they
shut up and they don't say anything
about kind of this encroaching,
you know, autocratic
system.
And it doesn't come from any one angle.
You know, all these people think, well,
it'll just it'll just I don't care. I'm
I'm people go, I'm from the right. It'll
come from the, you know, it'll come from
the right. It'll silence everyone I
don't like. And which you shouldn't want
anyway, but it will never work like that
because what is left and what is right
isn't fixed. It's changing. It's
changing. Three years ago, the
right-wing solidly supported Israel.
Right now, they don't.
Three years ago, it was unthinkable for
a majority of the right to have turned
against America's funding of Israel.
Now, you are seeing people under 40 on
the left and the right agreeing that
America should not be funding whatever
the hell Israel is doing. You know,
building uh you know uh you know, Las
Vegas on the Gaza Strip. Nobody's in for
that. Nobody's in for that. When the
Israeli finance minister comes out and
goes, "Hey, we spent a lot of money on
the war. We got to get paid back a
little bit. We're doing a real estate
project. It's on Trump's desk. It's all
fine. People under 40 are going, "Hey,
man. I don't I can't own a house. I
can't pay back my student loans. Why are
my tax dollars funding
you guys going and building Miami
in Gaza? Who's that for?
Who's that for? And why are people
funding it?" You know, if you work at a
7-Eleven
for 12 hours a day on your feet, dealing
with every drunk who walks in grabbing,
you know, they want a pack of
cigarettes, they want this, they want a
hot dog, they want, you know, you got
protein bar, whatever.
And you do that job, which is not an
easy job. Whatever job you do, but think
about that. And you're getting paid
whatever. I don't know what 7-Eleven
pays, but let's imagine it's not ideal.
Your tax dollars are going so that real
estate developers can build luxury
condos with like floating bathtubs in
Gaza.
There's no way anyone elected Trump for
this. There's zero possibility that
people elected Donald Trump so that
their tax dollars could go to luxury
real estate development in Gaza or in
Qatar.
It there's zero way
that any of this take a look at that.
To be fair, it does look nice. to be
fair, a little bit of an AI rendering,
but nobody elected him for that. And now
if you criticize that, they'll take your
visa if you're a foreign student.
They'll just shut you down. So, shut the
[__] up. Get out of here.
You know, so
Kimmel was losing money for ABC, maybe.
I don't know. I heard he wasn't. I heard
he wasn't making a lot of money, but I
heard he wasn't losing it. But but by
the way, whether he was or he wasn't,
who cares? He was losing it last week
and he wasn't off the air.
It's directly related to that joke. The
FCC commissioner said it. I don't think
it was a particularly good thing for
Jimmy Kimmel to say this guy was MAGA.
He wasn't MAGA. By the way, it's easily
correctable.
You can correct the record without
destroying someone's ability to speak.
This is something that you know you try
to die on the hill of this. Now the only
thing left in this country unfortunately
seems to be uh power.
Everybody thinking that Jimmy Kimmel
being removed and indefinitely suspended
from ABC means that you are winning.
You're a fool.
Your tax dollars are going to build
casinos in Gaza. You're not winning.
This is not what winning looks like. By
the way, Kimmel had planned to address
Carr's comments on his show Wednesday
night. According to people familiar with
the matter, before his on air
appearance, Dana Walden, co-chairman of
Disney Entertainment, spoke to the host
about his plan. The people said after
the conversation between Kimmel and
Walden, she and other senior executives
thought that the stars approach could
make the situation worse. people
familiar with their conversations said I
mean the one of these issues is that the
Kimmel writer room is a is a is a
monolith. I don't think there's anybody
in there that voices any alternative
opinion here and says maybe we should
slow down with this. Again, not a reason
for the government to get involved and
for the president to be threatening
other late night hosts. But there's an
element of of the of the rightwing
that that wants this stuff to keep going
on. And it's because they felt
culturally powerless for a very long
time. And they and they want these
institutions to kind of bend the knee to
the president. And it's happened in
other countries. People bring up Hungary
and Victor Orban and all that stuff.
Obviously people like Putin, nobody
wants to live in a country where a late
night comedian
um is,
you know, subject to removal because he
says something that the president of the
United States doesn't like. Also, here's
a sidebar. Is Jimmy Kimmel the deep
state?
You know, well, Tolsey Gabbard goes out,
who I like, but she goes out and goes,
you know, Obama's guilty of treason and
they don't really present a ton of
evidence and then they just drop it and
they move on and then they go, "Well,
this guy and that guy and this guy and
that guy and then the Epstein files,
they all vote to not release them." And
then they go, "Well, Jimmy Kimmel, let's
get him out of here." And then, you
know, Steve Bannon's got a documentary
with 20 hours about Epstein. We'll
release that.
You got all these hours. Nobody
over there. They all think you're
really, really dumb.
And they're treating you the way you
treat a young child who wants something
that they're not going to get. You try
to distract them with other things. You
could, you see, I don't have kids. I'm
around people that have kids all the
time, and they'll go, I want to do this.
I want to do this. I want to do that.
And then you go, "Hey, hey, hey. What
about this? Take a look at that. Isn't
this cool? Look, a dog.
This is that
this is that
I mean Ces Patel is walking around
like the most compromised person on
earth. If Cash Patel is not afraid of
something, I don't know what fear is.
These people are running around. They're
going to unmask everything and expose
everything and whatever. Again, I wasn't
the one who ran on that premise. They
were. And none of that has happened. In
fact, whatever coverup's going on,
they're extending it. They've now become
a part of it. They are helping
facilitate it.
Every comment under everything these
people post is, "What the [__] are you
doing?"
Speaking of a 7-Eleven, I don't think
Cash Patel could solve a robbery at a
7-Eleven without [__] it up. By the
way, it just the guy's the head of the
FBI.
I love Helix. I'm telling you, it's the
best mattresses in the world. Everyone
that comes and stays with me says, "Why
are these mattresses so great?" And I
say, "It's Helix. Go to the You got to
go." And this Labor Day sale is amazing.
It's too good. I'm telling you right
now, you will never regret getting a
Helix mattress. It is the best thing
that most people are going to have in
their house. I'm telling you,
everybody's sleep is better with Helix.
You get some nice fall air and a Helix.
You are good to go. It helps with
snoring, back pain, sleep apnea. It
helps you sleep through the night. If
you sleep too hot, it cools you down. Go
to helixleep.com/timd.
I'm telling you, helixleep.comtimd.
Make sure you enter our show name after
checkout so they know we sent you. Okay.
This the the the Labor Day sale is
killer. It's 20% off sitewide. Are we
nuts?
>> 25
>> 25% off sitewide. It just went up 5% in
a second. That's how good it is.
helixleep.com/timd.
It doesn't make any sense. I don't care
if you hate Jimmy Kimmel. I'm pretty
sure this administration when they were
when they came in and they were talking
about America first, they weren't
talking about Jimmy Kimmel. But this is
how they distract you from what's
actually going on. Let's get rid of
Jimmy Kimmel because he's pissed us off.
By the way, Sam Alman,
let's give him more and more money
because we're in an AI arms race. Well,
who does that help? got very I don't
know 20 people, 20 Trump voters
and they were all at that dinner in DC.
You know, is your life better? Are you
making more money? Do you feel better?
Do you feel financially more stable? Are
you excited about the Israeli uh real
estate project in Gaza? Does that does
that get you going? Do the renderings
make you happy? Get the renderings up
again. Do the renderings make you happy
you don't have healthcare? Do the
renderings do it for you? They're nice
renderings,
but does that make you excited? Is that
what you voted for? Is that what you're
happy about? Is this what you're excited
about? Do you show them to friends of
yours who have recently lost their jobs?
Do you show them the renderings and go,
"Take a look at that. That's going to be
pretty [__] nice." Imagine that. Some
of them you could walk right to the
beach. They'll probably have a long
boardwalk. You go right to the beach.
That's what this is about.
This city of the future that's being
built on the mass grave of all of these
people that we're funding. That's what
it's about. An AI city of the future
built on a mass grave. You're funding
that. Oh, Jimmy Kimmel said a a joke
that people don't like. Let's let's see
what this is. We're not even a year into
this administration. is very obvious
that this whole thing the wheels are
coming off. Tucker Carlson's become a
liberal hero. Is that cuz things are
going well? Is that cuz things are going
well? Is that be Is that Is that
happening because things have gone in
the right direction?
It's wild to watch. Every liberal friend
I know in LA, okay, cocoons themsself in
a blanket, drinks a matcha, and watches
Candace Owens for 19 hours a day. And I
like Candace, but is that because
they're doing a great job in Washington?
Is that because things are going well?
You know,
you know what I mean?
I'm just telling you, you have a
situation
here that's starting to look more and
more like a very big
OP.
that a lot of people
are going to be easily distracted
by Jimmy Kimmel
or whatever. We're still in the Ukraine
war. We're still doing this.
We're going
into World War II.
I imagine we're going into World War II.
How do you get out of this without World
War III?
How do you get out of the levels of
corruption being exposed without a world
war?
I hope we do. It would be nice to, but
how do you get out of it? It's clear
that a lot of people want a wider
regional conflict. I think Netanyahu
does. I think Putin does. And it would
be nice if there was someone in our
country who didn't. I I mean,
I don't know, but we're heading You can
feel it. The pieces are coming together.
We We see
different
parts of the world aligning
economically.
We'll see it militarily.
We see a lot of things happening that we
don't have a there's not a ton of
significance to some of these events,
but there will be later when you look
back and you go, "Yeah, that wasn't
good. That wasn't great. That didn't
make a lot of sense.
Russian warplanes breach NATO airspace
in dangerous provocation over Estonia.
Israel's bombing like 12 countries a
day.
We've got problems,
you know, all over the world. We have a
pamphlet being handed out, I believe, in
Taiwan saying, "E, everybody get ready.
Get ready. Everybody,
Taiwan issues handbook to prepare
citizens for Chinese invasion." Um, what
a lovely read.
What a nice read. Get ready. They're
coming.
So during all of this,
all of this is uh happening. We're
talking to Jimmy Kimmel, talking about
Jimmy Kimmel. And it's important to talk
about it's important to talk about me
being fired from Riad. It's the most
important thing perhaps
next to the World War II, you know, and
the fact that the people in charge of
the country believe it's their job to
colonize Mars and make us an
interplanetary species and you're not
getting a knee operation. You're not
you're not getting a knee operation
before they make us an interplanetary
species and colonize Mars. And a lot of
people in America think it's cool. They
think it's cool.
I mean, I I don't know what to tell you.
I don't know what to tell you. I really
don't. I don't know. I don't know what
to tell you. It's the It's the wildest
time that I've been alive, including co
in. Somehow
there's more of an eerie feeling now
than CO.
Somehow it feels like we're waiting for
something to happen. I don't know what
it is. It feels like that.
And not in a again, not in a crazy,
you know, Fibonacci sequence. What are
the numbers? What are the dates? Not in
that way, but just in a general sense of
malaise that people have. People have
this. You talk to people about it. You
go, how does it feel? Nobody feels good.
Nobody feels great about this. We aren't
in Listen, we've probably never been in
control. Now, it's obvious how little
control we're in.
It's really obvious. There's a group of
people, there's a group of oligarchs,
there's a lot of highly
placed interests that all have agendas
and they're all breaking bread and
they're all carving it up and there's no
and most people in this country
don't have much of a say. And you just
got to hope that they're they have your
best interest at heart.
You just got to hope that they're
they're that you figure into their grand
plan.
When Peter Teal or Sam Alman or any of
these people or you know Bezos or any of
these guys talk, Zuckerberg, when any of
them speak, you just have to hope that
they're like they're thinking about you.
They're thinking about you and your
family and your ability to pay for
things. Um they're already going out and
going, "Don't own a house. It's not for
you. doesn't make sense. Buy stock, buy
crypto. Why would you own a house? By
the way, not owning a house
hurts your social life. You can't have
people over. You can't sit in the
backyard with people. You can't talk to
them. You can't go, "Hey,
what's going on here?" You can't share
experiences with them. You live in a
tiny apartment. You're embarrassed about
it. Nobody comes over. There are no
social bonds. That's the point. That's
the point. You don't get to talk about
the discuss the the future of your
community. That's exactly the point. You
just sit there in your tiny little
apartment. I have friends in New York
and I did this for years when I was
doing comedy. You sit in your tiny
little apartment in New York City or
whatever city by the way, Cleveland,
doesn't matter. You sit in this little
apartment. You don't have anyone over
and you consume the internet.
Get online more and more and more and
more. It's a tiny little cell that you
live in and then you radicalize yourself
on the internet. Some of us are
schizophrenics. Go do crazy things. Then
the draconian surveillance and police
state comes in. They don't have an
interest in people having a yard. They
don't want you outside. They don't want
you outside.
It doesn't help them out.
putting your phone on, you know, in a
drawer and going outside and sitting
down with six people and having dinner
and talking about your community isn't
helpful to them. It doesn't make any
sense. They want you on the phone in a
cell that you rent.
They want you paying more and more money
every year for a cell.
And all of these companies related,
you know, all of these mega conglomerate
corporate landlords, everything's a
mall. Every They build these malls and
then on top of them they have apartments
that cost $6,000 a month to live on top
of insomnia cookies, pig.
Well, at Door Dash, really easy. They
just they just throw the cookie in the
window. It's disgusting.
No one should live like this. No one's
supposed to live like this.
And everybody thinks it's okay or it's
whatever. What did Jimmy Kimmel say? The
you're paying a lot of money to live in
a cell. You can't have friends over.
It's disgusting.
It's absolutely disgusting for most of
you to have your friends to your
apartment. It's embarrassing. It's
shameful. I've been there. I couldn't
have my friends to my apartment and my
friends are animals. And it was still
embarrassing to have your friends in
your apartment cuz it's a tiny little
apartment. You've got a a a corner of
dirty clothes. You have a takeout in the
garbage. It is a you live in a in a cell
and and then the behaviors of someone
who lives in a cell
are what they want. Someone who can sit
in their backyard and have a glass of
wine and invite the neighbors over and
go, "What's going on? How are you? What
do we feel? What's going on in the
schools? What's going on in our
society?"
They don't want that. They want you to
be afraid of your neighbors. They want
your neighbor to scare you.
That's what they like. They like the
idea that your neighbor terrifies you. I
have neighbors. They scare me.
I don't want to see them. I I I hope I
don't see them.
You know, that's how you destroy an
entire country. You don't you don't just
do it. You do it with the first with the
way people live. This is the way you
destroy a country. You make everybody
afraid of their neighbors, fearful.
You tell everyone, "Don't assimilate at
all. You don't have to. In fact, we
don't want you to. We don't want you
making friends with anyone. Why would
you assimilate?
Speak your own language. Have your own
customs. Do your own thing. Don't go
near anyone else. Don't assimilate.
Don't become an American. Don't think
like a a free American person. live in
the cell. There's a cupcake ATM. Get the
cupcake out of the ATM.
You know, you have to plan for the
unexpected. It's so important and and
especially for your your family, your
your children, husband, wife. Ethos. You
can get life insurance in minutes, not
months. There's no complicated process.
100% online. No medical exam required.
You just answer a few health questions.
Get a quote in as little as 10 minutes.
You can get same day coverage without
ever leaving your house. Life insurance
is more affordable than you think. With
Ethos, you can get a free quote and
customized rate that fits your budget.
You can get up to $3 million in
coverage. Some policies as low as $2 a
day build monthly. Ethos is a
trustworthy company that disrupts a
traditional life insurance industry. As
of March 2025, business insider named
Ethos, the number one no medical exam
instant life insurance provider. Three
million families have completed their
applications and trusted Ethos to help
find the right coverage. Ethos has 4.8
Eight out of five stars on Trustpilot
with over 2400 reviews. Protect your
family at Life Insurance from ethos. Get
your free quote at ethos.com/tim.
That's ethos.comtim.
Many people are struggling with hair
loss and I'm telling you the best way to
handle it is Neutrifull. Neutrifull's
number one dermatologist recommended
hair growth supplement trusted by over
one and a half million people. You can
feel great about what you're putting
into your body since neutrifil hair
growth supplements are packed by
peer-reviewed studies and NSF
content certified the gold standard in
thirdparty certification for
supplements. I'm telling you, see
thicker, stronger, faster growing hair
with less shedding in three to six
months with Neutrifll. For a limited
time, Neutrifull is offering our
listeners $10 off your first month
subscription and free shipping when you
go to neutrfull.com and enter the promo
code Tim Dylan. Find out why Neutrifull
is a bestselling hair growth supplement
brand at neutrfull.com spelled nut
t-r.com
promo code TimDillan. That's neutrfull
promo code Tim Dylan. T I M D I L L O N.
It really is just the way people live.
So when when these billionaires are
telling you you don't need to own a
house, it's not just that they don't
think it's a good financial investment.
Their interests are not served by you
having block parties and seeing other
people. They'd rather you live in a cell
where people bring you Thai food and you
watch YouTube videos about people or
reality shows about people that do have
homes.
That's what people do. People in Los
Angeles
go to their cell on top of a PF chs,
eat those lettuce wraps, which are good,
and then watch reality shows about
people that can afford to have a home.
That's pornography. Now, you you come
thinking about having a place to see
your friends,
but they don't want you to have any
friends. They don't want communities.
It's the hollowing out of the entire
thing that that serves their purposes.
And the only thing left is the bread and
circuses and the Kimmels and the this
and the that. It's the only thing left
and you're radicalized easily one way or
the other. And they're pulling strings
because you have less and less of your
own [__] You don't have a community.
You live in some global world where like
every single thing is the most important
thing and then you go online and go my
take and I
you're supposed to care about [__]
that's like in a 10b block radius of
where you live.
You're not supposed to be involved in
the Middle East. You're not supposed to
be funding a real estate project in in a
place you've never been in Gaza. It's
not natural. It's insane. You're just
not supposed to do that. You're supposed
to care about things. You're supposed to
know who got murdered two blocks away.
Why did that person get murdered? You're
supposed to know that. You're supposed
to be interested in the crime in your
area. Why? Because you live there.
But now that that there doesn't exist.
It's malls and cupcake ATMs. It's
[__] you know, private equity
companies that build, you know, mega
structures that look like storage
lockers. And you just sit there and get
mad all day on the internet and you
don't know your neighbors and you don't
care if they get murdered. In fact, you
might want them to. You have no stake in
the game.
And all of this
isn't new and it's being expedited at a
level I've never seen.
It has never been more obvious that they
are trying to get rid of human beings
and human relationships and human
communities at an incredibly
fast clip.
Human behavior puzzles them. Sam Alman
doesn't know what humans do.
Sam Alman's confused by human behavior.
He doesn't get it. He finds it
inefficient and messy.
It perplexes him. Okay,
this is and and allegedly that guy that
worked for him died in a real weird way.
Okay. And Sam Alman, when Tucker pressed
him about that, acted like I did when my
doctor asked me if I went to McDonald's.
So, let's get real here. These people
don't care and they think human behavior
is a problem. Cultural
practices that they don't understand.
They don't understand people going to
church. They don't understand festivals
and fairs. They don't understand uh
people having a community where they
exchange
goods and services in physical
locations. They don't understand people
that care. Their job is to make you
terrified and broke.
They want you on the citizen app. They
don't want another person telling you
here what happened to Bob. They don't
want that interaction happening. They
want you on the citizen app all day
hearing about crime that you don't care
about because your communities aren't
tight-knit communities where people know
and care about each other. They're
strange
corporate hellscapes
filled with like part-time residents and
and they've turned every city in this
country into a foreign Dubai like Disney
Wonderland where people can launder
money and and and and then take a bunch
of laundered drug money and go buy labu
smoothies at air. They don't want
anything resembling life.
It's obvious they don't want anything
resembling human life.
You're supposed to just walk around and
participate in some viral scam.
That's the only reason you exist to
these people. The only reason you exist
to Sam Alman is so that he can monitor
you in some way and that you can take
part will wittingly or unwittingly in
some viral scam
that someone's cooked up that you can
buy some food item or little critter or
cryptocurrency that someone is hawking.
That is the sum total of your humanity
to these people. Why buy a house? You
don't need a house. What a bad
investment. What does that word even
mean? Investment? What are you talking
about? You know what's a really good
investment? Sitting there with seven
people in your backyard having dinner
and talking about life. They don't want
it. It's a threat to them. It's actually
a big problem.
So, I I mean, it's at a it's a a
tremendous clip. It's at it it's the the
frequency of which this is happening,
how quickly it's happening everywhere.
It's not just any one thing.
It's architecture. It's it's it's um
it's business, it's political, it's
cultural, but really at the end of the
day, it's all of these things working
together to take you out of the world
and put you on the internet where they
want you to live. You're a view. You're
an anonymous source of data. you're
something to be marketed or or
terrified, but they don't consider you a
a person with inalienable rights. They
don't consider you um in in any form a
reflection of God or a greater
intelligence outside of the thing that
they're going to create.
They consider you an obstacle and that
the way you live is an obstacle to their
ultimate goals. That's what they
consider you. You are something that's
in the way. Your football game and your
a couple of beers outside or you invite
people over to your home. Your family,
your faith, your community, your
culture, your all of this to them. And I
don't care if it's a liberal or
conservative. I don't care if you're a
fundamentalist Christian. I don't care
if you're Jewish Muslim. I don't care if
you're an atheist. I don't care if you
do the winter solstice. They don't
either. Their entire thing is to get rid
of physical communities that are based
around these things and usher people
into a digital landscape
by telling them not to own houses, not
to drive cars, not to own things, to use
ride shares, to be on the internet, to
live in a cell, and to be happy. It is
what it is. You'll own nothing and be
happy. It's a famous article. We all
bring it up, but it's true. And
what Jimmy Kimmel says
at the end of the day doesn't really
affect your life in the way that you
think it does. He should have a right to
say it.
He should uh be criticized for saying
it. People should attack him
on the facts, not physically.
you should attack the facts because they
weren't present in what he said. Okay?
But there's something bigger going on
and everyone feels it and it worries me
that other people don't. There's
something bigger going on all over the
country and it's not about Jimmy Kimmel
and it's not really about left verse
right. It's about
this inertia
that's moving humanity into a perpetual
state of constant war,
depression, anxiety,
anger.
I'm not procilitizing. I'm not telling
you to do this or do that. I'm not
saying to you that you can only find
meaning in life one way. I believe
there's many ways to find meaning in
life. However, it's clearly obvious that
the algorithms are manipulating us to
hate each other and kill each other
while everyone else is building resorts
in other places of the world. In Gaza,
in Qatar,
they'll be building them in the Ukraine
soon. Watch.
And all the while your life gets worse.
You become
angry. You lack the ability
to live
the life your parents did or their
parents did.
And all they have to say to you is how
lucky you are.
How lucky you are that you don't live in
a place like China.
Wow. How lucky you are that you don't
live in a place like China. as they make
America more like China every hour.
So,
you know,
you just have to understand what's
happening.
You have to resist it in the ways that
you can. Don't listen to them when they
tell you not to buy a house. Don't
listen to them. Do not listen to them
when they tell you that it's worthless
to have a patch of dirt and grass and
friends and a community. It's absolutely
not worthless. In fact, it's the only
thing that may save you. Don't tell them
it's worthless to uh to learn how to
cook or or grow food or be sufficient
because everything is at the click of a
button. Don't tell them that it's
worthless. I mean, don't listen to them
when they say that it is worthless to
try to see the humanity in somebody who
doesn't agree with you. You know, it it
it really is disturbing. The people
right now that run the show are not
people
They make these mistakes. They do these
interviews. Guys, someone keep them
behind closed doors.
They keep being interviewed.
Frankenstein's keep coming out to be
interviewed. I think Frankenstein was
actually good. I I I didn't read that
book. Was Frankenstein good?
>> Yes.
>> Yes. That's not what I mean then.
Who was bad then in Frankenstein? The
mob.
>> Yes.
>> All right. That doesn't apply here. Why
did they fire me? It's not fair. But
what I'm what I'm telling you is this.
Take a minute. Charlie Kirk was a human
being. He was not a dangerous radical.
You may not have agreed with him. Who
gives a [__] The guy was a human being.
You have to rediscover that you are a
human being
as well. You don't have to like me. You
don't have to think I'm good. You can
hate me. You know, I'd like if you
didn't shoot me. But, you know, at the
end of the day,
getting rid of human communities,
replacing them with digital communities
that are created via hate
and algorithms and moving people out of
these
physical places and destroying the bonds
we have with each other. Be very
suspicious of people who tell you to not
own a home. Be very suspicious of people
that tell you they talk about
investments and they own 12.
Be very suspicious of all these people.
And I've been saying things like this
for a long time, but it does feel now
that we're getting to the point where
we're getting close to the point of no
return. And if we're easily distracted
and we're just fighting each other,
we're not going to be able to demand
that we stay human because there are
interests and agendas operating at very
high levels that want to rob us of our
humanity and they're winning and they're
succeeding.
I hope everyone has fun at the Riad
Comedy Festival.
I will continue to live like a Saudi in
my own country
because I can. I am now fully with Iran
against Saudi Arabia. I didn't want it
to be this way, but it is.
Alliances shift constantly. This is the
game. This is the game. I hope everyone
enjoys it. And if you're a Saudi, I hope
you continually continue to listen to
the program.
Continue to listen, continue to support
us here. And again, it's no reflection
on you. I blame
a few people who ended up being
cowardly.
I do not blame the Saudi people,
even the executioner who's doing the
behanding. I don't even blame you. I
don't blame you with the mask on doing
the behanding. I don't blame you. I
actually don't blame you. I don't blame
you. Truly, I don't blame you. Okay.
I blame Joker